MARIOM AKTER

Mobile: 01646526040

1216 Shewarapara, Mirpur Road, Dhaka Email: mariomakter.dev@gmail.com

https://www.linkedin.com/in/mariom-akter

I've completed my graduate in CSE with experience in PHP(Laravel)Developer, web development are Highly organized with strong IT skill including use of remote collaboration platforms and technology. Analytical, with good commercial awareness, interpersonal and customer service skills. Resourceful and keen to embrace new challenges. Work with team and cooperative for colleagues.

EDUCATION

BSc. In CSE, Green University of Bangladesh

Nov 2020 - Mar 2023

- Innovation and Sustainability: Web Design and Development
- Program Strategy: understanding use of technology update and many more
- Understanding Value and Values: explored content writing and guest posting

Chandpur Polytechnic Institute

Feb 2015 – Aug 2019

Department: Computer Technology

CGPA: - 3.47 out of 4.00

Meghdair Taheriya Fadil Madrasha

Dec 2015

Group: General science GPA: - 4.94 out of 5.00

WORK EXPERIENCE

Web design and Development Expert

Feb 2022 – Sep 2022

- Experience working with PHP, performing unit testing, and managing APIs such as REST
- Understanding OOP & MVC
- Knowledge of database design and querying using SQL...
- Proficiency in HTML, Jquery, Tailwind, Vuejs, Css3 and JavaScript.
- Designs and maintains social media presence. Website Management.

Content writing Expert, Guest Posting

June 2019 - Mar 2021

- Website Management, Organic Traffic Growth, SMM management
- Keyword Research, SEO Audit, Keyword Research, Content writing,
- Plagiarism Check, Website content Post

IT & DIGITAL SKILLS

Competent user of: Microsoft Word, Excel, PowerPoint, and Outlook

Basic skills in creating content for: Instagram, Twitter, Facebook, YouTube, Website

Confident using: client management systems, basic accounting software and databases

PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

Courses Completed:

Professional Web Application & Development, isdb-bisew, February 2022 Professional Web Design, Professional Web Design, Jan 2019 Basic PHP, *Udemy*, Feb 2023

Expertise Area

- HTML, CSS, Responsive Website Design.
- Experience working with PHP, performing unit testing, and managing APIs such as REST
- Best e-commerce website in Laravel
- MS Office, Data Entry, Empathetic analysis.
- Time management, Team Work, Customer knowledge.

INTERESTS

I love work for human. Gardening is one of the favorite hobbies.